<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<b:vehicles  xmlns:b="http://www.WebDev.nci/tutorial">
    <b:vehicle id="b1">
        <b:image>images/bikes/S1000RR-HP4.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>1</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/cZKfTgnzgaY</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>BMW S1000RR HP4</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>BMW</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                As if the standard S1000RR wasn’t good enough already, BMW have made it even faster, 
                lighter and more technologically-advanced, with this HP4 version. The jewel in the HP4’s crown is the new 
                electronic Dynamic Damping Control (DDC) suspension system, which adjusts the rebound and compression damping 
                as you ride along. It gives the BMW the perfect suspension setting whether you’re on a bumpy back-road or hammering 
                around a smooth racetrack. 
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>999cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>191mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>198bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.4secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>18,500</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>51mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b2">
        <b:image>images/bikes/CBR-1000.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>2</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/GMn0ihTM1IE</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Honda CBR1000RR Fireblade</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Honda</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description> 
                The big news for the 2009 Honda CBR1000RR Fireblade isn’t its new, oval-shaped indicators, 
                but its revolutionary electronically-controlled Combined ABS system. This makes the Honda Fireblade 
                the world’s first ever ABS-equipped superbike. This system takes none of the enjoyment out of riding 
                this incredible superbike and it feels just the same to ride as a normal Blade, even on the track. 
                The system stays in the background until the moment you get into a difficult braking situation, then the 
                ‘brake-by-wire’ kicks in.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>999cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>186mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>176bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.3secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>17,995</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>48mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b3">
        <b:image>images/bikes/ZZR-1400.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>3</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/FbfasHEwx3E</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Kawasaki ZZR1400</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Kawasaki</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description> 
                Simply put Kawasaki’s new ZZR is the new king of speed and power, beating the formidable Hayabusa hands down. 
                It produces more power and torque, and accelerates quicker than any other road bike but unfortunately is still 
                restricted to anb:specification agreed 186mph limit, but will get there in breathtaking time, hitting the limiter with ease, 
                still with plenty in reserve. Not just a one trick pony either, now comes with ABS, power modes and traction control 
                as standard.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>1441cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>201mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>200bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>1.8secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>16,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>47mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b4">
        <b:image>images/bikes/GSXR-1000.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>4</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/pR9Hkm3u8lc</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Suzuki GSX-R1000</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Suzuki</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                The now old GSX-R was an exceptional bike, winning AMA and world endurance 
                titles and narrowly missing out on a BSB title. Suzuki have simply improved the weak points, 
                namely better brakes, more midrange, lighter handling with a few cosmetic tweaks, which in the end produces an 
                exceptional road bike with real world manners. It may lack sophisticated traction control and ABS, and isn’t as 
                race-focussed as BMW’s S1000R or Kawasaki’s ZX-10R but it won’t be far behind in terms of lap times and is much more
                forgiving on the road
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>999cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>186mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>182bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.3secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>19,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>50mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b5">
        <b:image>images/bikes/ZXR-1000.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>5</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/UuPiTq4HjYE</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Kawasaki ZX-10R</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Kawasaki</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description> 
                Kawasaki’s ZX-10R evokes thoughts of rip-roaring power and handling best suited to race circuits. 
                While that may have been the case of the original 2004 model, subsequent models have been diluted to the point 
                where ZX-10R is regarded as a decent on the road superbike but not quite in touch with the competition of the latest Blade, 
                techno-laden R1 and BMW’s S1000RR. The 2011 Kawasaki ZX-10R is the bike to change this. 
                It is the first of the Japanese bikes to come out fighting against the storming BMW and, based on MCN’s first ride 
                (at Qatar’s Losail circuit), the Kawasaki’s superb blend of handling, braking, usable power and decent suspension will 
                make it a better road bike than the BMW.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>998cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>185mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>197bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>1.98sec</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>15,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>49mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b6">
        <b:image>images/bikes/GSXR-600.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>6</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/09rAyNIxp_Y</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Suzuki GSX-R600</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Suzuki</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description> 
                Suzuki has slashed an incredible 9kg from the 2011 GSX-R600. The engine has more midrange, 
                a close ratio gearbox and for the first time, Showa Big Piston Forks and Brembo monobloc radial front brakes. 
                Aside from a handful of components, the GSX-R600 is completely new. The easy-going nature of the bike is still there, 
                but it’s sharper, more agile and there’s more punch out of the corners. If only it looked a bit special and not look just 
                like any other GSX-R to be made over the past decade.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>599cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>176mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>125bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.9</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>13,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>54mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b7">
        <b:image>images/bikes/CBR-600.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>7</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/T0HRxdC8eYo</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Honda CBR600RR</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Honda</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                Honda has given its supersports weapon subtle tweaks for 2009, designed to give it more mid-range oomph and a 
                smoother power delivery. New pistons, cylinder head and exhaust system have bolstered torque between 6000-10,000rpm, 
                which makes the engine more flexible on the road. Luckily for us, this has been done without sacrificing any top-end power. 
                The big news, though, is the optional electronically-controlled Combined ABS system, which is a world-first for a supersports machine. A new-style bellypan now 
                covers the whole engine and the C-ABS valve unit for the front brake. The C-ABS version doesn’t detract from the 
                enjoyment of riding MCN’s supersport 2008 machine of the year, and it feels just the same to ride as the standard Honda 
                CBR600RR, even on the track
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>599cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>170mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>107bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.7secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>13,500</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>32mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b8">
        <b:image>images/bikes/ZXR-600.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>8</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/eF21f1JlYj4</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Kawasaki ZX-6R</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Kawasaki</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                In terms of chassis and handling the new Kawasaki ZX-6R a big step forward over the old ZX-6R. The new big piston 
                forks use MotoGP technology and make a huge difference. They take a little getting use to at first but enable you to 
                brake devilishly late yet the bike remains stable. Engine wise 115bhp at the back wheel makes it the most powerful 
                standard 600 we have ever tested, say no more.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>599cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>163mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>115bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.8secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>10,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>36mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Inline-4</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b9">
        <b:image>images/bikes/VFR-400.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>9</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/ox-yYLuJ4CE</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Honda VFR400R NC30</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Honda</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                The Honda VFR400R, or NC30 as it’s commonly known, is effectively a 400cc version of the iconic VFR750R (RC30) 
                and as such is a cheaper alternative to the RVF400R which succeeded it in 1994. It has excellent handling, still 
                looks good and a usable engine for road and track, although it’s not as quick flat out as some of the other 400 imports. 
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>399cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>128mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>60bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>3.2secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>6,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>39mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>V Four</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>

    <b:vehicle id="b10">
        <b:image>images/bikes/DUCATI-1098.jpg</b:image>
        <parameter>10</parameter>
        <b:video>//www.youtube.com/embed/zAbvbRESniI</b:video>
        <b:details>
            <b:name>Ducati 1098</b:name>
            <b:manuacturer>Ducati</b:manuacturer>
            <b:description>
                This is the Ducati motorcycle we’ve been waiting for since the original Ducati 916. It’s a Ducati motorcycle 
                in the truest form. Blood red, stunning to look at and absolutely pure in its purpose. It’s been a long time coming 
                but it finally looks like Ducati has built a sports bike that can run with the best. The Ducati 1098 finally stands 
                for what a Ducati motorycle means - pure unadulterated sports bike heaven.
            </b:description>
        </b:details>

        <b:specification>
            <b:engineSize>1099cc</b:engineSize>
            <b:topSpeed>185mph</b:topSpeed>
            <b:bhp>160bhp</b:bhp>
            <b:zero-sixty>2.2secs</b:zero-sixty>
            <b:cost>20,000</b:cost>
            <b:mpg>42mpg</b:mpg>
            <b:cylinders>Desmo V-Twin</b:cylinders>
        </b:specification>
    </b:vehicle>
</b:vehicles>
